noblemaster.com 2019-05-07

# Noble Master Games - Privacy Policy

## Noble Master LLC - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. 

### What information do we collect?

We do 

_not_

collect personal information such as a person's name, address, birth date, gender, email or phone number unless specifically entered by you. Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected, for example a purchase. 

Long-term data such as user IDs, passwords, signatures, settings, messages, avatars, games, ratings, awards and such is collected based on your interaction with our services and needed for proper function. 

Short-lived data including logins, languages, countries, operating system, versions, networking data and such is collected automatically and stored for a period of up to 24h after which the information is purged from our systems. We also employ a third party service "statcounter" for website statistics (no cookies). 

### What do you do with this information?

We will use specifically entered personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling the purposes specified. We never supply your personal information to any third parties, unless absolutely necessary, such as when the information is for example required for a credit card purchase or when we are required to do so by law. 

Long-term data is kept to ensure proper function while interacting with the network servers. The data is not parsed for personal information, but due to the public nature of some of the information, e.g. a chat message, it can be viewed by other users of the system. Don't publicly post information you don't want to be visible to others. We don't forward private data such as settings to third parties unless absolutely required. On the other hand, public information such as a chat message is visible by default to everyone. 

Short-lived data is anonymized for statistical purposes and open for viewing to everyone. It is also used to ensure stability of our network servers e.g. by preventing DDoS attacks, detecting hacking attempts, multi-accounting/cheating and such. This data is purged after 24h and not forwarded to third parties. Processed data that has been anonymized for statistical purposes is stored for a longer period of time. We use "statcounter" to help improve our applications and websites by looking at statistics such as screen sizes, operating systems, browsers used, incoming and outgoing links. 

### Is my information secure?

We have taken steps to ensure our databases are secure, and are confident in our ability to keep your information safe. For example, passwords are stored encrypted in our database. In other cases, we simply don't store personal data at all. If you have never entered your email address, which is e.g. needed for password recovery, we don't have it. 

Also, our servers do not store credit card or banking information. Payments are handled by third party providers such as Google, Apple, Amazon, Valve/Steam or Stripe which we believe are capable to handle such information confidentially. Sensitive data such as credit card payment information is transmitted encrypted. 

Rather than collecting data, our goal is to have our servers up and running reliably. In that sense we periodically purge stale data we don't need. Chat messages are not recorded in our database. Wall messages and private message are purged after half a year or so. Game data is deleted soon after completion. In general, anything that has become obsolete is purged periodically. 

### How can I access my data?

The information we have about you is yours. Contact us anytime to access, correct or delete information we have about you. Please, include the related **username(s)** for a speedy resolution. 

### Still have questions?

Also, we realize everyone has a different view on privacy. We take your privacy very seriously. If you still have concerns, or are unclear about any aspect of our privacy policy, please contact us, and we will be happy to discuss the matter with you.
